[{"answer": "Americans deserve an honest approach.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 7, "question": "So what are they waiting for?", "qSentId": 6}, {"answer": "Absolutely we do.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "I mean at the moment, as things stand, do you actually have any hope of doing a deal?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "Well, the only thing that can -- the only thing that can break this impasse, the stalemate, as the president talked about on Monday night, is compromise.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "Because something has to happen, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "I mean do you guys really appreciate how ridiculous this all looks to ordinary people?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "Well, what the president has always said is that we didn't get into this mess overnight, we're not going to get out of it overnight.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "And when you look at the unemployment figures at the moment you look at the potential crisis as it would be of the credit rating coming down, you know how much blame are you guys taking in there for where we are today?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "Well, we are -- we are certainly concerned about a potential downgrade.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "I mean are you concerned about that eventuality?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "He has -- people all across the White House have been in touch with CEOs around the country to talk about this.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "Has president responded to the CEOs yet?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "I'll tell you, it's a really strange mood, if you will, Piers.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "Are we heading towards any kind of this compromise the president talked about?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "We're stuck right now because we're talking about a financial deficit.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "Where are we?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "I would still say tonight that most of the people who have the votes and the power think it's unlikely.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "Could you imagine a scenario where actually the country does go into default or not?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Actually the speaker says he's made tremendous progress today and that we're narrowing in on those final votes.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "It's been a pretty awful day for the speaker, hasn't it?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "I mean you talked there about game changing, I think the American public are sick and tired of games for a start.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "But it is us sitting down and saying OK, what can we get through the Senate and on to the president's desk because we don't want to see America default?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "You must get a sense of that from the public that you meet, don't you?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "I would say that there are those that believe that this -- the plan that Boehner has brought forward doesn't go far enough.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "Would you agree with that?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "Well, because the short-term bill that has us going back at these three months from now when you've seen how much trouble it's causing now will just roil the credit markets, risk our credit agency, and tie up the Congress from doing other things like focusing on jobs and the economy.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "Senator, why are so fatalistic about this?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "Well -- I mean, you can talk about the economy.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "I mean the reality is that you guys have continued to preside over a tanking economy for a long time now and the point we can keep blaming President Bush and the Republicans is rapidly getting to the point where you can't do it anymore, isn't it?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "Well, here's the -- the ideal situation, frankly, is to just raise the debt ceiling which has been undone 39 times before by Republicans and Democrats alike.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "Wouldn't that be the master stroke here to say, look, I can't work with these intransigent Republicans for a second longer, the country comes first, I've got the power to do this, and I'm going to do it?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "Well, God forbid we default.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "If we get to next week and America does default, do you think the decent thing to do would be for all of you to resign?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "Well, frankly, right now, we have all kind of politics going on that are, as I call it, toxic.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "What is holding it up?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "First of all, the way we need to approach tax reform, which I think most of the experts acknowledge, is to reduce rates and reduce the tax expenditures accordingly, and then grow the economy through the kind of stimulative impact that that kind of powerful tax reform would have.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "Until there is less intransigence by the Republicans on that key thing, how can you talk about a great reformation?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "I don't think he's lost control, but it's very clear that the effort by the speaker to come through with yet another -- a third approach now to try to put something forward to the Senate that the Senate Democrats can accept is moving so far in that direction that he's starting to lose votes on the other side.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "Has he lost control?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "I think you summed it up quite nicely, Piers.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "What the hell are you lot playing at?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "It is, absolutely.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "And is that a precursor to what we may see going forward to election year?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "Somebody has to stand down.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "What happens?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "Scale of one to 100.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "John King, scale of one to 100 of political crises that you've covered over the years, where are we with this?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "When you were president of Mexico, could you ever have imagined a scenario like this?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "Well, it's incredible, because people are not thinking on the future.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "Why has the world's number one superpower got itself into such a terrible mess financially?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "It's a very worrying time.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "So where are we going to be leading the dream of the Founding Fathers of this nation?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "Dangerous game that is being played here.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "When you see the politicians on both sides, Democrat and Republican, squabbling now, trading insults and all the rest of it, with such a serious situation so close, what do you think of that?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "Well, he has to negotiate.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "If you were President Obama, and you've been a president of Mexico for six years -- if you were in his shoe right new and you're facing a 14 trillion dollar debt in this country, what can he do quickly to try and sort things out, do you think?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "Oh, yes, no doubt.", "docId": "110728pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "If it was a business, would it go bankrupt the way things are going?", "qSentId": 547}]